<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on ARTSEY</title>
    <link>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on ARTSEY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/new_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/new_website/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the New Website#We have launched a new website powered by Hugo The new website will host this blog and documentation for the ARTSEY system.
Github Repo#Our new new github repo is also up. This repo will store information about the system as well as the contents of this website. The repo will allow more complete collaboration on the system by contributors from the ARTSEY community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2020 Update</title>
      <link>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/december_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/december_update/</guid>
      <description>December Update.#Development of ARTSEY is continuing. The layout has reached a relatively mature state and I am now beginning to design dedicated hardware.
We have a handful of users who have reached 20 WPM on ARTSEY, and the discord server (see link below) is more active every day with discussion of ARTSEY and other experimental typing methods. I am personally up to nearly 50 WPM max and can easily sustain 40 WPM without extreme focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Alpha Combos</title>
      <link>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/alpha_combos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/alpha_combos/</guid>
      <description>Memorizing the Alpha Combos#Memorizing the alpha combos may seem difficult. It is easier to learn the letters in groups. There are patterns that will help with this:
Notice the relationship between the first B chord option and C. They are only one key different and the B chord looks a little like a b when viewed from the side. Note that the second B chord is a little easier to hit so you may want to migrate to using that chord once you have everything memorized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chosing the Base Letters</title>
      <link>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/base/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gleorepo.github.io/posts/base/</guid>
      <description>Choosing the Base Letters#The first task in designing the system was choosing the base letters. The main goal was getting common letters on the base keys. The secondary goal was to provide a memorable name for the system that could also serve as the URL.
Using the excellent analysis by Peter Norvig as a starting point, I decided A,E,I,O, and T had to be on base keys with some of H,N,R,S as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
